The mantra of this course is that the best way to learn is by doing, and we will be doing stuff together
이번 수업의 만트라는 가장 좋은 학습 방법은 행동이라는 겁니다 수업 내내 함께하게 될
throughout.
거예요
There will be eight commercial projects which will be applying what you're learning to real business
8개의 상업 프로젝트가 있는데 여러분이 배운 것을 실제 사업 문제에 적용할 겁니다
problems, and they'll be exercises for you to do the same thing.
그리고 같은 것을 하는 연습을 할 거고요
And I'm hoping that you'll be able to set up GitHub and be able to make your own versions and push them
여러분이 깃허브를 설정해 자신만의 버전을 만들어 푸시하고 PR, 끌어오기
and send me a PR, a pull request, and I'll be able to merge in your code so that other people can
요청을 보내시면 여러분 코드에 병합해 다른 사람들도 솔루션을 볼 수
see your solutions too.
있게 할게요
But you'll be able to add this to your GitHub and be able to show yourself that you are building projects
하지만 이걸 깃허브에 추가해 현실 세계의 상업적 문제를 해결하는 프로젝트를 만들고
to solve real world commercial problems.
있다는 걸 보여줄 수 있어요
One of our projects I mentioned is going to be a chatbot assistant.
제가 말씀드린 프로젝트 중 하나가 챗봇 비서가 되는 거예요
We're going to build one for an airline.
항공사에도 하나 만들 거예요
It's going to be able to do things like use tools to look up the price of tickets.
툴을 이용해 티켓 가격을 검색하는 그런 작업을 할 수 있어요
It's going to make audio and it's going to show pictures like this beautiful pop art version of London
오디오를 만들고 사진을 보여줄 겁니다 이 아름다운 팝아트 버전 런던처럼요
showing here on the right as you interact with the chatbot assistant.
여러분이 챗봇 비서와 상호 작용할 때 오른쪽에 보이는 거죠
We're also going to be building rag pipelines, putting vectors of information in a vector data store
래그 파이프라인도 만들 겁니다 벡터 데이터 저장소에 정보의 벡터를 넣는 거죠
that you'll have running, and we'll be able to look at things like visualizations of the vectors,
벡터에 대한 시각화 같은 걸 살펴볼 수 있을 겁니다 3D
mess around with them in 3D space, look into them to understand how different kinds of information
공간에서 그걸 뒤흔들고 살펴봐서 다양한 종류의 정보가 어떻게 벡터 공간의 다양한
get placed in different locations in vector space, and why that is fundamental to Rag retrieval, augmented
장소에 있는지 이해할 겁니다 왜 그게 대량 회수, 증강 세대에 필수적인지도요
And then, as I say, the the moment, the big moment in the project will be in week eight, when we
말씀드렸듯이 프로젝트의 핵심은 8주 차에 찾아옵니다 에이전트
will build an Agentic AI solution that will bring together everything that you've learned about through
AI 솔루션을 개발할 때죠 지난 8주간 여러분이 배운 모든 것을 하나로
the eight weeks for something which will solve a business problem.
합쳐 사업상의 문제를 해결할 거예요
And I'll be able to give you some examples of how you can then apply that to solving other business
여러분이 미래에 직면하거나 오늘 직면할 수 있는 다른 비즈니스 문제 해결에
problems that you might face in the future, or that you might have today.
어떻게 적용할 수 있는지 예를 들어드릴 수 있어요
And you'll be able to watch as agents collaborate, you'll see the memory of the agents and see what's
요원들이 협력하는 모습을 볼 수 있을 겁니다 요원들의 메모리와 요원 세계에서
going on in our agent world.
벌어지는 일을 볼 수 있죠
A lot to look forward to.
기대가 커요